





SUMMARY

Front-end developer who specializes in UI design. Taps into all aspects of art, design, and interface. Operates the full gamut of front-end design with a versatile skill-set. On the creative side, executes visually appealing graphics, layouts, and animations; on the technical side, codes fluid, responsive websites with cross-browser compatibility. Improviser, troubleshooter - I learn on the fly. If making websites is like the tango, I'm ready to dance.

C	1/	ī	н	1	C
7	IN.	н		-	- 7

HTML5	Maya
CSS3, SASS, & LESS	ZBrush
JavaScript & jQuery	Unreal Engine
PHP	Quixel Suite
Git	Flash
Photoshop	
Illustrator	
Sketch	

EMPLOYMENT

Freelance Web Developer & Graphic Artist

June 2009 - Present

Manages site creation from concept to final execution for small business and portfolio websites. Supports services that include themes for blogs and social platforms, mobile app interfaces, branding, and graphic design.

UI Developer at Uguru

August 2015 - December 2016

Created company website pages; collaborated early and often with the front-end and technical team to prototype interfaces for mobile and desktop apps. Leveraged user flow and animation to smooth out pain points and optimize delightful experiences. Designed icons and other graphic components for interface and branding. Intiated best practices for the company style guide, animation, and coding.

Administrative Assistant at Jones L. Wee, CPA

January 2002 - September 2012

Managed telephone services, scheduling, and mailing services; assisted in spreadsheet creation, payroll services, tax return input, and document filing. Organized file management system and provided IT support for all hardware.

EXPERIENCE

Guild Romance Game

July 2015 Yurei Shrine

July 2015

Developed a dialogue-driven flash game on a team by implementing UI elements, designing graphics, and compiling a documentation system.

Created a simple puzzle-solving flash game based on a haunted, Asian-inspired shrine. Modeled all elements in Maya, textured and lighted in Unreal Engine, and programmed in Flash.

EDUCATION

B.ASc. in Game Art & Design from SAE Ex'pression College

September 2012 - January 2016

VOLUNTEERING

Graphic Designer at Chinese Independent Baptist Church of Oakland

February 2013 - Present